<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Blog>
	<Entry author="Nathan Campos">
		<Title>Introducing the plainBlog</Title>
		<Date>25/06/2011</Date>
		<Image>images/jquery.jpg</Image>
		<Content format="html"><![CDATA[jQuery is a fast and concise JavaScript Library that simplifies HTML document traversing, event handling, animating, and Ajax interactions for rapid web development. jQuery is designed to change the way that you write JavaScript.]]></Content>
	</Entry>
	
	<Entry author="Nathan Campos">
		<Title>A-Team (2010)</Title>
		<Date>25/06/2011</Date>
		<Image>images/a-team.jpg</Image>
		<Content format="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Amazon.com Review</h3>
		Give it up to the A-Team: they've always been good at demolishing things in big, big ways. Freed from the confines of the 1980s TV series, the 2010 blockbuster movie version allows the four members of the paramilitary squad to really amp up the mayhem to newly crazed heights. Liam Neeson plays team leader Hannibal Smith (inheriting the cigar-chomping from the show's George Peppard), and pro wrestler Quinton "Rampage" Jackson is "B.A." Baracus, the TV show's most iconic character (insert Mr. T "I pity the fool" joke here). As the vain Face, Bradley Cooper preens in convincing fashion, and District 9 out-of-nowhere star Sharlto Copley plays the unhinged pilot "Howlin' Mad" Murdock. These boys are on the trail of some money-counterfeiting plates, from Bagdad to Germany to places in between. It would be understating it to say that the plot is not of primary importance, although Patrick Wilson has some fun as a CIA official and Jessica Biel occasionally strikes poses as Face's ex-flame, now a military officer displeased with the A-Team's extra-legal shenanigans. The storytelling is insipid and half-hearted--but when it comes to snarky dialogue and two-fisted action scenes, director Joe Carnahan is in his comfort zone. It's reasonably fun watching the working-out of such logistical puzzles as dropping a tank (with crew inside) from a plane, or scattering the main characters on a dockside as cargo containers rain down from a ship looming above them. Good times, although is it asking too much for certain basic laws of physics (if you drop a human body ten stories, for instance, it might actually sustain injuries) to be used as a guideline? But worrying about such matters isn't in the spirit of The A-Team, which cheerfully ignores the petty concerns of credibility and logic. --Robert Horton]]></Content>
	</Entry>

	<Entry author="Nathan Campos">
		<Title>Introducing GitHub For Mac</Title>
		<Date>25/06/2011</Date>
		<Image>images/github_logo.png</Image>
		<Content format="html"><![CDATA[    Pull requests, merge button, fork queue, issues, pages, wiki &ndash;&ndash; all awesome features that make sharing easier. But those things are only great <em>after</em> you've pushed your code to GitHub.

		<p>Today we're happy to announce <a href="http://mac.github.com">GitHub for Mac</a>.</p>

		<h3>What does it look like?</h3>

		<p>When you first launch GitHub for Mac, we'll help you set up your GitHub account and find repositories already on your computer. From there, you can start managing repositories.</p>

		<p><a href="http://github-images.s3.amazonaws.com/blog/2011/mac-screenshots/home-full.png"><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/e5d0a458cb69aba17a98f0da2b51e5a8afaf145e/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f686f6d652d63726f707065642e706e67"></a></p>

		<p>Once you dive into a repository, you'll be able to view the commit history just as you would on the web.</p>

		<p><a href="http://github-images.s3.amazonaws.com/blog/2011/mac-screenshots/commits-full.png"><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/a50150079a28c1334c37190f5c4b5f979fe2681e/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f636f6d6d6974732d63726f707065642e706e67"></a></p>

		<p>And you can of course dive in to a specific commit to see the diff and perform some operations.</p>

		<p><a href="http://github-images.s3.amazonaws.com/blog/2011/mac-screenshots/commit-full.png"><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/dbedf3f226ce05a76b8c4a47232cad04b1c8c0c8/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f636f6d6d69742d63726f707065642e706e67"></a></p>

		<p>Once you've made some changes, you'll be able to create commits.</p>

		<p><a href="http://github-images.s3.amazonaws.com/blog/2011/mac-screenshots/changes-full.png"><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/b6ea0739d4acc2cb94d73739ef2a6d65b93f7c44/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f6368616e6765732d63726f707065642e706e67"></a></p>

		<p>When you want to change branches quickly, press ⌘ + B and a branch selector will show up.</p>

		<p><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/4db3535996781edc0d93b5cda101194cf662fa18/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f6272616e636865732d706f706f7665722e706e67"></p>

		<p>Changing branches automatically stashes any changes until you switch back to the branch &mdash; switch branches with wild abandon. If you need to publish branches to GitHub, create a new branch, merge branches, or delete branches switch on over to the branches tab.</p>

		<p><a href="http://github-images.s3.amazonaws.com/blog/2011/mac-screenshots/branches-full.png"><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/e4791e26acd20f225cbae3b550700a2129c8f085/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f6272616e636865732d63726f707065642e706e67"></a></p>

		<p>Once you're ready to share your commits, or pull in remote commits &mdash;&nbsp;just press the Sync Branch button. We'll perform a smarter version of <code>pull --rebase &amp;&amp; push</code> that reduces merge commits but doesn't rewrite your merges.</p>

		<p><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/78fac20d873ee2bb8937ae6fd4969ca1cd4de8d6/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f73796e632d627574746f6e2e706e67"></p>

		<h3>Automatic updates</h3>

		<p>Once you download GitHub for Mac, we'll send out updates and the app will automatically download them. Keep an eye out for a little upgrade notice with a list of changes.</p>

		<p><img src="https://a248.e.akamai.net/assets.github.com/img/5fb5b7dadf9cfffb44240fbdb7f6623266825860/687474703a2f2f6769746875622d696d616765732e73332e616d617a6f6e6177732e636f6d2f626c6f672f323031312f6d61632d73637265656e73686f74732f757067726164652e706e67"></p>

		<h3>Behind the curtains</h3>

		<p>GitHub for Mac wouldn't have been possible without some awesome open source projects:</p>

		<ul>
		<li><p><a href="http://libgit2.github.com/">libgit2</a> powers much of the Git operations for the app, making every interaction smooth, responsive and <em>fast</em>.</p></li>
		<li><p><a href="https://github.com/libgit2/objective-git">objective-git</a> libgit2 bindings bridge the gap between Cocoa &amp; libgit2.</p></li>
		<li><p><a href="https://github.com/BigZaphod/Chameleon">Chameleon</a> powers a good portion of the GUI. We're working with the Chameleon guys to get our changes into the main project, but in the mean time you can check out <a href="https://github.com/joshaber/Chameleon">Josh's fork</a> with all our modifications.</p></li>
		</ul><h3>Just the start</h3>

		<p>This is just the beginning &mdash; we're really stoked for the future of GitHub for Mac and hope you will be too.</p>

		<p></p><center><a class="button classy huge" href="http://mac.github.com"><span>GitHub for Mac 1.0 is free and available today</span></a></center>]]></Content>
	</Entry>

	<Entry author="Nathan Campos">
		<Title>Introducing the Test of plainBlog</Title>
		<Date>25/06/2011</Date>
		<Image>images/github_mini.png</Image>
		<Content format="html"><![CDATA[Testing the HTML formatting things like <b>Bold</b>, <i>Italic</i> and <u>others</u><br />
Second line with <a href="http://google.com">link</a>]]></Content>
	</Entry>
</Blog>